Guide to the Mary Dowdell Ashley Film Collection, 1937-1975 RL.10048
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Films, 1936-1967; 1
  - Reel 4, compilation, segments 37-48, 1962-1965; 4
    Reel 4. Sequence 40. Scene 2. Montgomery, AL, downtown: Sidney Lanier High School parade.
    Reel 4. Sequence 40. Scene 3. Montgomery, AL: Floyd School: cheerleaders with Bonnie closest to camera; football being played; audience scenes.
    Reel 4. Sequence 40. Scene 4. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: Myrick, dressed-up wearing tie & red blazer; Ann, dressed up & holding purse & Bonnie (behind Ann) dressed up & has bouffant hair-do; Ann in vest with designs & black skirt; Shap in navy blazer & Myrick again; Daddy in grayish suit & dark shirt. Schatzi (wirehead dachshund) in all of these scenes. Bankhead Avenue: Big Ann in short fur cape getting out of her car parked in front of house; greets Schatzi; Myrick & Big Ann in driveway in front of a car;?? Car out on street: Myrick, Shap, Big Ann, Ann & Bonnie.
    Reel 4. Sequence 40. Scene 5. Bankhead Avenue, back yard: Shap and friends playing basketball -- ?? May be Shap's birthday.
    Reel 4. Sequence 41. Scene 1. Montgomery, AL: Floyd School: girls playing softball.
    Reel 4. Sequence 41. Scene 2. Lynchburg, VA: Randolph-Macon Woman's College (RMWC): Ginny's graduation: procession in gowns; procession of girls in white, called "daisy chain;" Rosie Pittman followed by Ginny (white headband) followed by Pat Nunnelley. Scene with Daddy (blue/gray suit), Shap (white jacket), with Big Ann behind him, then Ginny & Pat Nunnelley; dark scenes; then Shap, Bonnie (blue jacket), Mother (white hat), & Ginny; then see Ann behind Shap; scene with Bonnie, Big Ann (white skirt) & Ginny; really dark stretch.
    Reel 4. Sequence 41. Scene 3. Montgomery, AL, Thomas Avenue: Neill's pool with lots of kids ???
    Reel 4. Sequence 42. Scene 1. Romar Beach, AL (near Gulf Shores): Nan Holley (?) in 2-piece bathing suit; Little Ann on beach & Edward; Nan Holley in 2-piece suit on back on sand; Daddy in shorts & shirt walking on beach to Little Ann & Edward; Ann in red suit & wrapped in black & white striped towel, next to Nan Holley; Myrick & ? in water with close-up of both; Ginsie (?) & Uncle Eddie coming out of water; Ann in 2-piece red bathing suit walking into water.
    Reel 4. Sequence 42. Scene 1. Romar Beach, AL (cont'd): Ginsie holding a fish with inner tube & standing in the water; Daddy in trunks with towel on shoulders & golf cap on, standing at the edge of the water; mother in dark swim suit on right, Little Ann in swim suit & big hat & Edward; Ann & another standing in water; Myrick's friend on all 4's on sand with Little Ann & others in background; Ginsie in inner tube in water; Myrick & friend, etc. playing on sand -- close-up of Myrick and friend.
    Reel 4. Sequence 42. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue: ? in dark glasses, Mother, Bonnie (horizontal striped top) & ?; then on Bonnie's right, Susan Selman & ? In dark glasses, Sydney Smith on Bonnie's left, then Mother & Shap; Ann holding puppy with Sydney on her right & Shap on her left; group: person holding dark glasses, Susan Selman, Sydney Smith, Ann, Bonnie.
    Reel 4. Sequence 42. Scene 3. Perdido, AL: skiing at the Point; on boat: George Harris (no shirt), Bonnie, Ginny & Ann climbing in; Ann sitting (can see her feet) & Ginny on right; Myrick getting off ski; water scenes including skiing; boat: ?, Ann & Bonnie; close-up of Bonnie (black thin straps to bathing suit); Myrick & Ginny beside boat & ? on boat. Note: could not identify Mark Wilson, who is listed as being in film.
    Reel 4. Sequence 43. Scene 1. Montgomery, AL: downtown: Sidney Lanier High School Homecoming Parade -- Marshall Lumber Mill Co. truck --quite DARK.
    Reel 4. Sequence 43. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue, front: Bonnie (?) on red bicycle; sidewalk to house: Bonnie (brown suit) & Marcia Jackson (plaid coat), then at front door.
    Reel 4. Sequence 43. Scene 3. Coosa, AL: Bottom: picking turnips --Myrick & Shap & friends; see Daddy in red plaid shirt; close-up of Myrick; scenes of friends of Myrick or Shap -- Julian Hart in bluejean shorts & reddish shirt; loading car; Daddy talking with John A. Dunlap; close-up of Shap (in Camp Laney t-shirt) holding a turnip; Myrick & ? holding box of turnips; red shirted friend leaning over Randolph Candler (?); car scene: Mother in yellowish top & friend ? Henry Seawell? in striped shirt; fair amount of DARK.
    Reel 4. Sequence 43. Scene 4. Bankhead Avenue, back yard: Daddy (blue/red plaid shirt) cooking in back yard; flowers & plants in yard.
    Reel 4. Sequence 44. Scene 1. Location?: 2 females.
    Reel 4. Sequence 44. Scene 2. Coosa, AL: Myrick, Mark & Bart Wilson ? sitting on white car -- white t-shirt & blue jeans; front of house: Myrick's friends & Daddy in hat; Myrick's friends eating; close-up of Shap? In blue jacket; Jack's Creek: Big Ann (gray hair); Uncle Eddie carrying 2 cokes; then Daddy & Uncle Eddie; Little Ann & Myrick; Jack's Creek area: Daddy, Uncle Eddie, etc.; shot of Mollie (pig tails) & Ginsie; then Myrick sitting & Ann D. next to Uncle Eddie; Big Ann standing -- her back to Daddy's back; Edward sitting & pointing -- plate of food in front of him; several shots of Stausses; Ginsie (white shirt) kneeling next to food plate; some dark scenes; more of Stausses -- Ginsie & Edward sitting on edge of rock.
    Reel 4. Sequence 44. Scene 3. Location ?: Gulf (where exactly).
    Reel 4. Sequence 45. Scene 1. Location ?: Gulf (where exactly): ??, then see Ann on right holding white towel; on left: Daddy in trunks; dark but close-up of Myrick eating ice cream on stick; picking sea oats: Shap on left, Ann (design shorts & blue top).
    Reel 4. Sequence 45. Scene 2. Coosa, AL: house -- ? on steps; DARK.
    Reel 4. Sequence 45. Scene 3. Gulf (exactly where): Bonnie on low chair, Gray Thames (blue/green/white bathing suit) standing; Myrick & Shap snorkeling; Bonnie standing; Shap coming out of water with snorkel; Shap holding arm out & friend in red/white trunks.
    Reel 4. Sequence 45. Scene 4. Bankhead Avenue, front porch: ? & ? with school books & then standing in front; Shap (plaid pants) & John Springer ? & Eddie Mosely?
    Reel 4. Sequence 45. Scene 5. Coosa, AL: The Falls: Sitting on rock near the falls: Alice & Withers Davis & behind them Daddy & Mother; ? standing; falls; group: Daddy (in glasses) & ????
    Reel 4. Sequence 45. Scene 6. Bankhead Avenue, 2 doors down: Thetford home -- Judge Thetford cooking stew -- not good shot of him; Daddy in tie.
    Reel 4. Sequence 45. Scene 7. Bankhead Avenue: back yard: red tile table -- Bonnie on right & Myrick on left; Daddy with back wall in background; side yard: Mother by banana plant.
    Reel 4. Sequence 46. Scene 1. Destin, FL: Gulf: Shap in dark glasses & Bonnie lying on back; Gulf sand & water scenes; ? in black bathing suit & Ann on right; more water & sand; Shap "acting up" & then playing with ? in black bathing suit; Ann with towel around her.
    Reel 4. Sequence 46. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: Shap (plaid blazer) & Ann & Bonnie (blue dress) & Daddy & Myrick (white blazer); Mother at left of screen.
    Reel 4. Sequence 46. Scene 3. Montgomery Country Club, tennis courts: Ann might be on closest court, where doubles match is being played.
    Reel 4. Sequence 46. Scene 4. Location?: Horses.
    Reel 4. Sequence 46. Scene 5. Bankhead Avenue, driveway: Mother beside truck & Daddy beside her at back of truck; Myrick &/or Shap & friends???; Mother beside driver ? Daddy?; DARK.
    Reel 4. Sequence 46. Scene 6. Gulf? In red, white, blue hat.
    Reel 4. Sequence 47. Scene 1. Destin, FL: Gulf -- Jack Tar Motel: Myrick & friend on beach; friend of Shap's flying kite on beach; Myrick's friend flying kite; Daddy & Ginny (red bathing suit); Shap & friend on sand.
    Reel 4. Sequence 47. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue, back yard: flowers in bloom; Daddy, Bonnie, Shap, Myrick; Daddy & Mother; Shap & Bonnie; driveway: Bonnie ? riding bike to street; DARK stretch; chairs in driveway/carport; Joe or Pat Thetford playing with hunting dog; Shap playing ping pong; Myrick & friends getting into car.
    Reel 4. Sequence 47. Scene 3. Hull Street: Little Ann (blue denim dress) walking to car; Uncle Eddie at back of car, unloading; Daddy, Mollie or Ann D. hugging Big Ann.
    Reel 4. Sequence 48. Scene 1. Destin, FL: Bonnie & Shap beside car; Myrick (trunks with white waisteband); Daddy (blue/yellow/white, etc. shirt); Uncle Eddie walks towards car with cooler & small suitcase; Edward on steps; Little Ann (white/gray/yellow dress) with back to camera; Daddy facing camera; back of Shap? in foreground; side of Bonnie's red hair (Bonnie in long t-shirt with 25 on back)???; Mother sitting on steps with camera case in lap.
    Reel 4. Sequence 48. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: Myrick & horse; Bonnie with ? on horse; others walking around; Bonnie riding on lot across the street -- can see 3516 house in background; Bonnie, etc. playing touch football in lot across street; Myrick &/or Shap's friends -- riding bikes on Bankhead; front yard: Mr. & Mrs Hart.
    Reel 4. Sequence 48. Scene 3. Location?: parking lot of ? Holiday Inn?; Margie Livingstone on left & ? on right; ???parents of friend of Ann's; Mother in beige coat with purse on arm; Margie & Ann.
    Reel 4. Sequence 48. Scene 4. Location?: Pat Thetford "acting up" with Myrick behind him.
    - Original 16mm film, 1962-1965; 1300 film feet (Box 1, Film-reel RL10048-F16-0004)
  - Reel 5, compilation, segments 49-58, 1960s; 5
    Original notes on can: 49: Ann's graduation - Mary Baldwin College. Big Ann in swimsuit. Perdido; 50: Perdido - Big Ann diving at Point. Mother and Dad sailing. Coosa - frozen falls. Bull Fight - Spain. Coose w/Stausses at Spout; 51: Shap and Friends. Bonnie's graduation at Converse. Bankhead. Perdido; 52: Coosa House - dark. Washington and Lee - Rick's graduation. John A. at Coosa - Bonnie and Mike at Coosa; 53: Southwest - S. New Mexico and California w/Darnelles Horse Races; 54: Shap's graduation at Duke. Shape and Exie; 55: Darnelles - Surfers in California. Bag Piper at Ross Clan Reunion; 56: Ann w/Patrick and Exie. Bonnie, Mike, Don and Ginny. Pond at Coosa w/Baby Patrick. Big Ann, Exie, Irma - Easter and egg hunt w/Dow. Mike, Bonnie, Dow and Ashley on boat; 57: Bonnie, Mike and Family at flower gardens. Mobile Bay. Cuernevaca, Mexico; 58: Cuernevaca, Mexico. Bankhead - Ginny, K.C. and Harris Family.
    Additional description: Reel 5. Sequence 49. Scene 1. Staunton, VA: Ann's graduation from Mary Baldwin: outdoor setting for the graduation ceremony. Procession of students across the stage & followed by faculty; Ann crossing to receive diploma & others receiving diplomas; close-ups of some, Ann holding hat on & people mingling after ceremony.
    Reel 5. Sequence 49. Scene 2. Location ?: Gulf (exactly where?): Big Ann (back to camera) in swim suit in water; facial view; close-up of fiddler crab & close-up of scallop shell; boat & then dog (German shepard variety) on beach; beach house with Big Ann (bathing cap) & Ann ? coming down steps; front of beach house: Ann on left, Big Ann, ? male?
    Reel 5. Sequence 50. Scene 1. Perdido, AL: at the Point: Big Ann on pier & then diving off diving board; sailboat with Mother & Daddy; ?female? Standing on beach with same dog as on reel #49; males on beach; close-up of Daddy leaning against pole & holding paper cup; beach prop-up: Daddy sitting on left with several female friends: Bonnie on his right & Ann sitting on sand in front but back to camera.
    Reel 5. Sequence 50. Scene 2. Coosa, AL: Daddy (?); close-up of ice in creek below falls & then falls with ice.
    Reel 5. Sequence 50. Scene 3. Spain: bullfight; lot of BLANK.
    Reel 5. Sequence 50. Scene 4. Coosa, AL: Ginsie; Edward; at the Spout: Bonnie, Little Ann (striped pants), Uncle Eddie; Ginsie & Edward in foreground with Big Ann on left with back to camera & Uncle Eddie leaning to left; Little Ann sitting down; Big Ann on right with Bonnie to her right & Daddy holding cup to her right; close-up of Little Ann in glasses & holding cup; Uncle Eddie standing. Those listed eating lunch.
    Reel 5. Sequence 50. Scene 5. Location? Someone's yard: person in chair may be Algie Neill
    Reel 5. Sequence 51. Scene 1. Location? Shap on left with friends on right; Julian Hart may be one in striped shirt.
    Reel 5. Sequence 51. Scene 2. Spartanburg, SC: Bonnie's graduation from Converse College: Daddy in white on left & Bonnie on his right with their backs to camera; Bonnie (lovely red hair in these shots) in graduation gown; Bonnie on left & friend on right & then Mother in white on right; ? in green/blue dress & then Bonnie on her right; Converse buildings & fountain; other people; Bonnie on left & Daddy to her right.
    Reel 5. Sequence 51. Scene 3. Bankhead Avenue, driveway: Backs to camera: Myrick to left & Daddy on right with Shap behind him & Exie on right; close-up of Myrick with mustache; Shap (brown pants) on left & Exie on right & then Myrick on right; Daddy with tie & then to left, Myrick & Shap.
    Reel 5. Sequence 52. Scene 1. Coosa, AL: house -- DARK -- trees, etc. near house with some of trees not in darkness -- lot of darkness.
    Reel 5. Sequence 52. Scene 2. Lexington, VA: Myrick's graduation from Washington & Lee (W & L): Myrick on lawn with crowd of people in background; people/building scene; ? in black tie & spectacles on left; Myrick with mustache in red plaid coat; youth in gown & tie & ? on right; female (?) & male in black tie again; youth in front; then some of Myrick's friends; to far left, Mother & Ann; people sitting outside for ceremony; graduation procession: scene of graduating seniors; Myrick receiving diploma -- shakes hand of person giving it & then walks off.
    Reel 5. Sequence 52. Scene 3. Coosa, AL: John A. Dunlap on tractor -- maybe Myrick's head in foreground; behind house (John A.'s?) --John A. on tractor & Myrick beside it; Tootsie leaning out car window; flowering tree & bird's nest in tree; Coosa woods: backs of Mike & Bonnie, Bonnie with bucket & then Mike; Myrick (?) with backpack.
    Reel 5. Sequence 53. Scene. California: Mother's trip to visit the Darnelles: highway scenes; rocky landscape scenes; station wagon on highway; Darnelles' (?) house: street scene with palm trees; rocky landscape scenes; station wagon on highway; ? House with red flowering ?; Darnelles' (?) dog; female & male in parking lot; newspaper vendors -- maybe outside horse racing stadium; horse racing scenes.
    Reel 5. Sequence 54. Scene 1. Durham, NC: Shap's graduation from Duke University; front of Chapel -- think see Ann & Ginny in light colored dresses; Chapel; Shap (with glasses) in graduation gown with Ann on right & Ginny (with glasses) on left; crowd of people -- Page Auditorium; Terry Sanford in academic robe -- Shap, Ginny, Ann (backs) on right & then 3 turn around; Sanford; front of Chapel entrance -- ? shakes Sanford's hand & they talk & then someone puts medal with chain around his neck; procession of students to Chapel; Shap minus gown with Ann & Ginny walking towards library -- crosswalk behind bus stop; football stadium (Wallace Wade Stadium) where graduation ceremony takes place.
    Reel 5. Sequence 54. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue: Shap & Exie.
    Reel 5. Sequence 55. Scene 1. California trip (cont'd): surfers; male carrying red raft; female in green sitting on beach; surfing; 3 people on beach: male, female in pink/red suit & male in rubber suit.
    Reel 5. Sequence 55. Scene 2. Wetumpka, AL: Ross Clan reunion: bagpipes; tractor pulling trailer with hay & kids on top; people walking -- think Bonnie (red hair); bagpipes again; people walking into woods; lots of darkness -- maybe in woods; outside of house (Crommelins?); lots of people.
    Reel 5. Sequence 56. Scene 1. Birmingham, AL (?): Ann holding Patrick with Exie & perhaps Ann's nurse behind; Exie with Ann & Patrick & nurse (?) to right; nurse (?) holding Patrick; Exie holding Patrick.
    Reel 5. Sequence 56. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue: Bonnie holding Dow, & Mike; Ginny on right of Bonnie & Dow; Dow trying to walk.
    Reel 5. Sequence 56. Scene 3. Coosa, AL: perhaps at pond on Ann's property: Ginny with Ann holding Patrick; Donald into scene from right.
    Reel 5. Sequence 56. Scene 4. Bankhead Avenue: Exie taking Dow from Big Ann & holding him; Irma behind Big Ann; Bonnie into scene; Exie holding Dow's hand as he walks; Bonnie (brown ?), Irma, Dow, Exie & Big Ann.
    Reel 5. Sequence 56. Scene 5. Location? Easter egg hunt: Dow holding egg; ? & young girl in lacy white dress; Dow & ?; Mike holding Ashley.
    Reel 5. Sequence 56. Scene 6. Location? On boat: Mike with Dow behind & Bonnie holding Ashley.
    Reel 5. Sequence 57. Scene 1. Mobile, AL: Bellingrath gardens: Mike, Bonnie, Ashley & Dow.
    Reel 5. Sequence 57. Scene 2. Location?: Beach (?): Ashley with bucket on beach, Bonnie on right & ? standing; another baby on left -- Ashley to right -- Dow coming out of water; Ashley on right & ?baby on left; Mike in sunglasses in water with Dow; Ann in multi-colored suit holding Patrick (?); Ginny? in red, white, blue striped cover-up; Ann & Patrick; Dow in front of Mike?; Bonnie with Ashley; back of Shap. Pier; close-up of Dow; Shap walking in water & on right Ann holding Patrick; Bonnie holding Ashley on beach; close-up of Ginny's profile; Bonnie carrying Ashley.
    Reel 5. Sequence 57. Scene 3. Cuernavac, Mexico: Bonnie, Ashley, Ann to right in pinkish skirt & blouse; homes? In Cuernavaca; Bonnie (white dress), Ann in pinkish dress, Patrick?, Dow? On left & Patrick? On right.
    Reel 5. Sequence 58. Scene 1. Cuernavaca, Mexico: small pool; close-up of Shap?, Patrick? & Ann on right; Shap in water & Bonnie holding Ashley in water; shots of various in water; Mike? in chair beside pool; more shots of most in water; scene with Shap (green shirt) in chair by pool & Bonnie beside Dow as he swims. Market scene; street scene with cars; marketplace; pool scene with no one there.
    Reel 5. Sequence 58. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue: Bonnie, Dow holding red umbrella, Ashley in dress with Bonnie behind her; Dow & Ashley; Casey, Ginny, Bonnie, Mike in front of banana plant with Dow in front; Ashley.
    - Original 16mm film, 1960s; 1100 film feet (Box 1, Film-reel RL10048-F16-0005)
  - Reel 6, compilation, segments 59-62, 1939; 1967; 6
    Original notes on can: 59: 1967 - AEA - Henry Seawell - Destin. Stausses at Bankhead. Destin w/Quisenberrys. Coosa - Exie and Shap; 60: Old Montgomery - Mule wagon - Baptism 1939 - Shorter, Alabama; 61: Kodak shorts; 62: Inaugural Parade - Montgomery - Governor Patterson (?)
    Additional description: Reel 6. Sequence 59. Scene 1. Destin, FL (?): Henry Seawell (red hair) & Myrick standing; Myrick - flip; motel?; Myrick & Henry in car & then they walk from hotel; Daddy (plaid jacket) loading plymoth station wagon; beach -- Henry on left & Myrick on right.
    Reel 6. Sequence 59. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue: Stausses: Edward with red band around waist & then Little Ann (beige sweater) in background; Ginsie with Edward; dachshund, "Peanut" (Stausses' dog) with Little Ann in background; Mollie in yellow, holding cat, probably Phoebe (Ashley's cat); Little Ann with Ann D. (blue sweater), partially hidden; driveway with Stausses' blue station wagon; Uncle Eddie & Daddy; Bonnie (in white) on right & then Ann D. to her right with Little Ann coming into scene, then with Edward & Ginsie kneeling and eventually Mollie on right; "July," Ashleys' chihuahua & "Peanut," Stausses' dachshund; Edward, then Ann D., then Bonnie with Ginsie on shoulders & Mollie in green sweater.
    Reel 6. Sequence 59. Scene 3. Destin, FL: Beach with Big Ann in swimsuit and towel on head, walking up steps; ? (male) Quisenberry with raft on head and then with female, maybe his wife,?, joined by Daddy on right; ? female sitting on sand with ?male Quisenberry on right & then ? (female) Quisenberry & Daddy; Bonnie lying on raft on stand & ? in water.
    Reel 6. Sequence 59. Scene 4. Location?: Mother in chair
    Reel 6. Sequence 59. Scene 5. Coosa, AL: ? male friend of Shap or Myrick; Myrick in blue shirt; friends of Myrick & Shap eating.
    Reel 6. Sequence 59. Scene 6. Bankhead Avenue: Driveway with Myrick; Exie & Shap with banana plant on left; Myrick holding bird, then Pat Thetford on left with Ann or Bonnie ? & Myrick.
    Reel 6. Sequence 60. Scene 1. Montgomery, AL: Street scenes in the vicinity of Perry Street: mule wagons, people walking & near end of scene, a bicyclist (some DARK areas).
    Reel 6. Sequence 60. Scene 2. Shorter, AL: Black baptism with viewers on hillside and baptism in pond at bottom of hill.
    Reel 6. Sequence 61. Scene 1. Kodak shorts (commercial films): The Early Bird & the Worm; Algiers; Felix in Hollywood; Charlie Chaplin in Easy Street; Wild Puppies; Rin Tin Tin in the High Country.
    Reel 6. Sequence 62. Scene 1. Montgomery, AL: Inaugural parade: Governor Patterson (?): downtown, at some point Dexter Avenue towards capitol with ceremony in front of capitol (very DARK in many places).
    - Original 16mm film, 1939; 1967; 375 film feet (Box 1, Film-reel RL10048-F16-0006)
      Preservation
      Sent to AV Geeks for Flashtransfer digitization on May 22, 2014. Returned from AV Geeks with raw video MOV and MP4 MOV, June 13, 2014. - Craig Breaden
      MD5: b5d5377765010a8a855709871cf44d60
  - Reel 7, 1950-1951; 7
    Original notes on can: 1950-51 - Gulf - Thetfords and Chandlers; Mother catching fish; Hull Street - Ginny, Ann Bonnie playing, Rick at 4 weeks; Easter Egg Hunt - Perdido - Dot and Billy fishing. Exie holding Rick in basket; Bonnie on sled, Perdido; Girl's camp (Talahi) Bonnie, Ann and Rick at Mary Esther; Ginny swimming. Thanksgiving Parade.
    Additional description: Reel 7. Sequence 63. Scene 1. Mary Esther, FL: Walking across Santa Rosa Island to the Gulf: Thetford, Candler, & Ashley families. Gulf: in water -- Dot Thetford with Bill in background; Ginny in white front & blue back swim suit; Louise Candler: arms? stretched out & Randy walking in water in back; Daddy & others in water; Ginny swimming; group in water.
    Reel 7. Sequence 63. Scene 2. Destin, FL: scene of fishing boats at docks; Daddy in blue shirt; Mother sitting on top of boat reeling in a fish; skipper helped out when fish to boat; pier after fishing trip: Daddy holding fish caught.
    Reel 7. Sequence 63. Scene 3. Mary Esther, FL: Ginny on diving board -- dives in & swims; Ann in red inner tube & Ginny in water; Daddy, etc. on beach.
    Reel 7. Sequence 63. Scene 4. Montgomery Country Club: swim meet.
    Reel 7. Sequence 63. Scene 5. Hull Street, back yard: DARK. Bonnie on left & Ann on right eating at small table; Ann on swing; Bonnie (blue dress) walking; Ginny & ? throwing ball.
    Reel 7. Sequence 63. Scene 6. Hull Street, front yard: Bonnie in snowsuit, Ginny (yellow scarf) behind & Ann in blue with red trim jacket; some DARK.
    Reel 7. Sequence 63. Scene 7. Hull Street: Mother in chair holding Myrick; weather warmer than in previous scene.
    Reel 7. Sequence 63. Scene 8. Hull Street, front & back yards: Bonnie in white dress on white chair; Ann in yellow dress brings chair (striped canvas). Lots of grown-ups & children: birthday party (Ann & Bonnie's) egg hunt; table with birthday cake -- Ann & Bonnie.
    Reel 7. Sequence 63. Scene 9. Hull Street: Daddy holding Myrick.
    Reel 7. Sequence 63. Scene 10. Location? Daddy dealing with bait in small boat; Anne & Frank Harris & Daddy on land adjacent to pier; Dot & Billy Thetford in boat fishing; in another boat, Daddy at motor with Anne & Frank Harris in boat.